Inventory of the William X. Scheinman Papers
Hoover Institution Archives
- Audio Tapes, 1959-1966. (Folder 51)
  - Phonotapes (Contd.). Recording of a speech by Tom Mboya, 1959 (Folder 56: 1)
- Phonorecords, 1959 (Folder 56)
  18 records of speeches by Tom Mboya, Calypso music, gospel music, and the Kenyan national anthem
  - Speeches by Tom Mboya, 1959 (Folder 56: 2-16)
  - Calypso song in honor of Tom Mboya (Folder 56: 17)
  - Gospel music (Folder 56: 18)
  - Kenyan national anthem (Folder 56: 19)
- Moving Picture, 1959 (Folder 57)
  1 film of an interview with Tom Mboya conducted by Bishop James Pike, 1959
- Oversize File, 1990 (Folder 58)
  10 maps of Africa and one calendar depicting South African children's art, 1990
- Poster, n.d. (Folder Art racks)
  1 framed poster depicting Martin Luther King, Jr.
- Closed Materials (Folder 59)